http://www.colonialcandle.com/pages/privacy

Back
Classic ScentsM. BakerOak RoomOval JarsCylinder JarsFarmhouse
Everyday Luxury
Back
Everyday LuxuryManly IndulgencePop of ColorColonial LuxeEveryday Luxe
Aromatherapy
Back
AromatherapyGaiamColonial ZenEssential OilsWellness Collection
Collections by Colonial Candle
Back
Collections by Colonial CandleManly IndulgencePop of ColorCobwebTravel CollectionInspire CollectionExpressions Collection
Back
JarsOval JarsWooden Wick JarApothecary Jars3 Wick JarsCylinder Jars
We Believe In Maintaining Your Privacy
Here at Colonial Candle®, Your Privacy is Important.
Security/Credit Card InformationColonial Candle® provides a secure online ordering for your protection and ease of mind. Your name, personal information and your credit card number are NEVER stored on the Internet with our system. Once you type your information, it is sent, encrypted, directly to a computer system that is NOT on the Internet. Privacy StatementHow your privacy is protected is important to you, and to Colonial Candle® as well. All your personal information is stored in an “offline” environment. At no time is any customer information accessible through the Internet. Visitor InformationWhen you visit us, our site automatically recognizes your Internet service provider. Other information that is automatically gathered is related to the number of pages you visit and the amount of time you spend on our site. We review this information to improve our website and to help us tailor our site to your needs. Information Provided by YouWe may use your email address for the following purposes: we may contact you with questions about your candle order or we may be responding to questions that you have asked us. With your permission, we may send email notices to you regarding new candle products, weekly specials, or online promotions. We will not rent or trade your email address to other companies for any reason. Any other personal information that you may provide to us as part of a survey will only be looked at as part of a larger pool of similar information from many other customers and will always remain confidential. This information will be used to help us improve our website and to identify products and services that may be of interest to you. What Are Cookies and Why Do We Use Them?Cookies are very tiny text files that are stored on your computer when you visit certain web pages that record your preferences. Colonialcandle.com uses cookies to keep track of what you have in your shopping cart and to remember you when you return to our store. They cannot harm your computer and we do not use cookies to store any personal or financial information about you on your computer. You can set your web browser so that you will always be notified when you receive a cookie. What Information Do We Collect? Why Do We Need It?There will be certain times when we will need to ask you for personal information, such as to complete an order. You can access most pages within our website where we will not ask you any information about yourself at all. This Privacy Policy will cover those times when we do need to ask you for personally identifiable information and how it will be used once you give it to us. We May Collect Your Name, Address and Phone Number.When you order from www.colonialcandle.com, we will need your name, street address, telephone number or other “offline” contact information. We will need this information to complete and support your orders from the colonialcandle.com website. This information may be disclosed to our staff and to third parties only if they are involved in the completion, delivery or support of your order or your use of the colonialcandle.com website. We May Collect Your Email Address.We may request your email address, or other information needed to contact you online. We use it to complete and support your orders from and use of the colonialcandle.com website, to respond to any questions you might have and to provide you with information about specials occurring on the www.colonialcandle.com website if you have opted-in to receive it. This information may be disclosed to our staff and to third parties only if they are involved in the completion, delivery or support of your order or your use of the colonialcandle.com website. We May Collect Purchase Information.We may collect information generated by the purchase of a product or service, like payment method. We use this information to process your order and support your use of the www.colonialcandle.com website. This information may be disclosed to our staff and to third parties only if they are involved in the completion, delivery or support of your order or your use of the colonialcandle.com website.
We May Collect Navigation and Path Data.As you browse our websites, we may gather navigational and Path data that shows what pages are visited and how long various features are used. This information will not reveal your identity or be linked to you personally. This information is used to analyze trends and statistics about how our visitors use the www.colonialcandle.com, it is not used to track individual movements. We may also collect another aggregate (non-personally identifiable information) about our visitors, such as gender, age or income. This information would be given to us voluntarily, such as during a survey, and cannot be determined simply by visiting our website. Are There Certain Instances Where This Information May be Disclosed?On rare instances, we may disclose your information if we believe it is necessary to protect our legal rights, if harmful conduct is threatened to You, MVP Group International, Inc. or if MVP Group International, Inc. is served with valid legal processes, such as a subpoena, search warrant, statute or court order, or if colonialcandle.com or shopcolonialcandle.com believes that membership has been used to commit unlawful acts or acts that may endanger the health or safety of another user or of the general public. How Do We Protect The Information You Give Us?Protecting your order information is a priority for us. Your name, personal information and your credit card number are NEVER stored on the Internet with our system. Once you type your information, it is sent, encrypted, directly to a computer system that is NOT on the Internet. In addition, we use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology to protect your online order information. If you wish to check the security of your connection, look at the lower left-hand corner of your browser window after accessing a secure server. (You will likely not be on a SSL until after you have added something to your shopping cart, or when you start checking out). If you see an unbroken key or a closed lock (depending on your browser), then SSL is active and the server is secure. You can also double-check by looking at the URL of your browser. When accessing a secure server, the site address will change from “HTTP” to “https.” Some browsers and firewalls won't permit communication through secure servers. This means you will not be able to connect to the server and won't be able to place an order through a secure connection. If this is the case you can always contact our customer service department at 1-866-445-9993 to place your order. Can You Change Your Information or Ask Not To Receive Any Additional Information From Us?We respect your right to have your personal information only used as you would have intended from us. If you are not interested in receiving information from colonialcandle.com, we will not send it to you. Please let us know by calling our customer service center at 1-866-445-9993 or by sending us an email. We will need to know your email address, full name and what information you no longer wish to receive. You can also use the same phone number and email if you need to update or correct your mailing address, phone number, email address or other personal information. Acceptance of The TermsBy using the colonialcandle.com website, you agree to this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy supersedes any earlier version. If you do not agree with anything stated in our Privacy Policy, please do not use the colonialcandle.com website. We may change our Privacy Policy by posting a new version of the policy on this page. It is your responsibility to review it frequently.
Sign in
Sign up
We've sent you an email with a link to update your password.
A password reset email has been sent to the email address on file for your account, but may take several minutes to show up in your inbox. Please wait at least 10 minutes before attempting another reset.
No account yet?
Registering for this site allows you to access your order status and history. Just fill in the fields below, and we’ll get a new account set up for you in no time. We will only ask you for information necessary to make the purchase process faster and easier.
Create an Account
Login
